(Amy:)You know, Sheldon,
(Amy:)instead of fixating
on what Bert has,
(Amy:)you should appreciate
(Amy:)all of the good things
in your life.
Y-You've got love,
(Amy:)you're in good health,
(Amy:)you've got a roof
over your head.
(Leonard:)Yeah,
(Sheldon:)but you've got all those things,
(Sheldon:)and no one's lining up
to be you.
(Amy:)Anybody else want to try?
(Amy:)I'm gonna go
make some more tea
(Amy:)and question
my life choices.
(Leonard:)You're up.
(Penny:)This is getting old fast,
Dolores, knock it off!
(Sheldon:)Uh, do you really think
(Sheldon:)calling me names is helpful?
I do!
(Penny:)Your life is fine,
you big baby!
(Sheldon:)Maybe you're right.
Really?!
(Leonard:)If it helps,
I'm questioning
(Leonard:)your life choices, too.
(Sheldon:)Thank you, Penny.
(Sheldon:)You know, I just need
to keep reminding myself
(Sheldon:)that Bert's success
is not my failure.
(Penny:)There you go.
(Sheldon:)And that men
of his large stature
(Sheldon:)are more susceptible
to a wide array
(Sheldon:)of life-threatening diseases.
(Penny:)There you go...